https://cso.gov.tt/privacy-policy/

Skip to content[seopress_breadcrumbs] Privacy PolicyLast updated: July 03, 2015Central Statistical Office (herein referred to as “CSO”, “us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the cso.gov.tt website (the “Service”).This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use the CSO website.Information Collection & UseWe do not collect or ask for any of your personal information on the CSO website. We ask only for basic contact details in the Data Request, Meeting Request and Contact Us pages for the sole purpose to follow up on your requests, comments and queries.Log DataWe collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.Google AnalyticsIn addition to web server logs, our websites use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Reports obtained from Google Analytics are used to help improve the efficiency and usability of our websites.Google Analytics uses cookies to gather statistics about how the website is accessed. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers located outside of Trinidad and Tobago.Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of our websites, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf.By using these websites, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner described in Google’s Privacy Policy and for the purposes set out above. You can opt out of Google Analytics if you disable or refuse the cookie, disable JavaScript, or use the opt-out service provided by Google.CookiesCookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.We use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.Automatic InformationWe automatically receive information from your web browser or mobile device. This information includes the name of the website from which you entered our Website, if any, as well as the name of the website to which you’re headed when you leave our website. This information also includes the IP address of your computer/proxy server that you use to access the Internet, your Internet Website provider name, web browser type, type of mobile device, and computer operating system. We use all of this information to analyze trends among our Users to help improve our Website.Links to Other SitesOur Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.Changes to this Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.PoliciesPrivacy PolicyTerms of UseRecent News
World Statistics Day, Tuesday October 20th, 2020 October 14, 2020
CARIBBEAN STATISTICS DAY 15 OCTOBER 2020 October 14, 2020
Protected Areas – A necessary economic driver July 31, 2020
Statistics in Focus: Trinidad and Tobago’s National Population and Housing Census July 29, 2020CSO director: Good PR helps people open up for surveys October 21, 20191 (868) 624-70011 (868) 625-9726AboutAbout UsHistory of CSOContact UsHelpData RequestMeeting RequestF.A.QSitemapFollow UsFacebookInstagramYoutubeCopyright© 2020 Ministry of Planning & Development. All Rights Reserved.Privacy PolicyTerms of Use
Scroll to Top
